Narrator: Part 1
Host: Hello, everybody, and welcome to today’s What’s My Job?
On team A, we have Nadine, Tyler, and James.
Nadine, Tyler, and James: Hello.
Host: And on the B team, Alice, George, and Charlie.
Alice, George, and Charlie: Hello.
Host: Team A, you start.
Today’s mystery guest is Mike.
You each say who Mike is and what he does, but only one story is true.
Team B, you need to decide who Mike really is.
Remember, you have one minute to ask Team A questions,
and then 30 seconds to ask Mike questions. Are we ready?
Teams A and B: Yes!
Ready!
Host: So, let’s welcome Mike.
Team A.
Nadine, please introduce him.
Nadine: Mike’s my hair stylist.
We like to chat a lot.
Host: And, Tyler, please introduce Mike…
Tyler: Mike’s my dentist.
He’s a very good dentist.
Host: And finally, James, please introduce Mike…
James: Mike’s the chef at my local restaurant.
I often have lunch or dinner there.
Host: OK, Team B.
You have one minute to ask Team A questions.